<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_title">Developer FAQ</string>
    <string name="faq_who_am_i_title">Who is the developer?</string>
    <string name="faq_who_am_i_answer">I am the independent developer behind YummyTV. I work on the app in my free time because I want to make watching anime more convenient and enjoyable.</string>
    <string name="faq_why_this_app_title">Why is the app like this?</string>
    <string name="faq_why_this_app_answer">YummyTV reflects my idea of a convenient anime streaming app. It evolves gradually: I try ideas, see how they work in real use, and improve them over time.</string>
    <string name="faq_why_not_all_cases_title">Why can’t I anticipate every case?</string>
    <string name="faq_why_not_all_cases_answer">My time and access to devices are extremely limited, so I cannot test every Android version, device model, video source, network, and user scenario in advance. I also do not earn any money from this work and develop the app entirely in my free time.</string>
    <string name="faq_why_errors_title">Why do errors happen?</string>
    <string name="faq_why_errors_answer">The app depends on more than its own code. External APIs, players, source availability, network restrictions, and device-specific behavior can all change or occasionally work differently than expected. Sometimes I may also have simply overlooked a feature or scenario.</string>
    <string name="faq_missing_site_feature_title">I’m missing a website feature, such as ABC</string>
    <string name="faq_missing_site_feature_answer">The app was originally created around my own needs on a TV, where many website features were simply unnecessary. I later added a mobile version, where almost all website functionality could technically be recreated, but I do not want to add features without a real need. If something is missing for you, please let me know — I will consider your use case and try to add the feature.</string>
    <string name="faq_unsupported_player_title">Why isn’t player XYZ supported?</string>
    <string name="faq_unsupported_player_answer">Most likely, I simply have not had time to get to it yet. If a player does not work or is not supported, please tell me the title, episode, and player name. I will try to investigate and add support for it.</string>
    <string name="faq_external_player_title">Why can’t I use an external player?</string>
    <string name="faq_external_player_answer">Many streaming providers do not expose a simple direct video link. Playback may require specific request headers, cookies, temporary tokens, and an active session. Obtaining and passing all of this correctly is difficult even inside the app, while an external player usually has no knowledge of these requirements and therefore cannot play the video.</string>
    <string name="faq_not_official_title">Why is this an unofficial app?</string>
    <string name="faq_not_official_answer">I am not affiliated with the website’s owners and develop YummyTV independently, so the app is not official. In the future, though, it would be great to establish a partnership and perhaps become official one day.</string>
    <string name="faq_why_feedback_title">Why is feedback important?</string>
    <string name="faq_why_feedback_answer">Your messages help me discover scenarios and errors that I cannot reproduce myself. The more precise the report, the easier it is to understand the cause and prioritize improvements that really matter.</string>
    <string name="faq_feedback_button">Questions, ideas, and suggestions</string>
    <string name="faq_expand">Expand answer</string>
    <string name="faq_collapse">Collapse answer</string>
    <string name="faq_open_repository">Open GitHub</string>
    <string name="faq_repository_url" translatable="false">https://github.com/Helandy/YummyTV</string>
</resources>
